Now, where were we?
Here we are.
Speaking of quiz material
and thinking about glass
as a potential problem
on tomorrow's quiz, yes.
You might want to know
about some of the things
we talked about Monday.
Here's an example.
OK, here's a question.
I have two glasses.
They form from liquids,
and they're cooled
to some temperature I call T1.
And I tell you
that T1 is greater
than Tm, which is the melting
point of the material.
Now remember, the melting
point is the same.
It's a number.
The melting point of
silica, that's a number.
But when the material
forms a glass can vary.
Why does a glass form?
Well, a glass forms--
this is what we
covered on Monday-- it
can form because of three
different things, right?
One is the crystal complexity.
That's important.
Another is the viscosity.
And the third is
the cooling rate.
Those are the three
things that we covered
on Monday for reasons
why a glass might form,
and then we started kind of
talking about the cooling rate.
That's what we
need to understand
to answer this question.